Guide to the James Jesse Strang Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Section D: General Correspondence
  - 323. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Bath Mills, [Mich.,] Mar 19, 1849, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. foolscap. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 324. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Albion, Mich., Jun 26, 1849, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 325. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Springport, [Mich.,] Jul 31, 1849, to James J. Strang at Voree. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 326. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Lapeer, [Mich.,] Aug 7, 1849, to James J. Strang. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 327. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Albion, [Michigan], Aug 16, 1849, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. foolscap. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 328. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Boston, Nov 20, 1849, to James J. Strang at Baltimore. 4 p. 8vo. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 329. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Boston, Nov 22, 1849, to James J. Strang at Baltimore. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 330. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Salem, Mass., Nov 22, 1849, to James J. Strang at Baltimore. 4 p. 8vo. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 331. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Boston, Dec 15, 1849, to James J. Strang. 4 p. 8vo. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 332. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Boston, Dec 22, 1849, to James J. Strang at Baltimore. 4 p. 8vo. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 333. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Boston, Jan 1, 1850, to James J. Strang at Baltimore. 5 p. 8vo. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 334. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Albany, Jan 16, 1850, to James J. Strang at Baltimore. 4 p. 8vo. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 335. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Albany, N.Y., Feb 7, 1850, to Jamas J. Strang, at Baltimore. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 336. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Williamsburgh [N.Y.,], Feb 13, 1850, to James J. Strang at Washington, D. C. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 337. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated New York, Feb 28, [1850], to James J. Strang at Philadelphia. 1 p. foolscap. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 338. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Williamsburgh, [N.Y.,] Mar 1, 1850, to James J. Strang. 2 p. 8vo. in pencil. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 339. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Buffalo, Mar 7, 1850, to James J. Strang at Williamsburgh, N.Y. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 340. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Attica, N.Y., Mar 13, 1850, to James J. Strang at New York. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 341. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Buffalo, Mar 21, 1850, to James J. Strang at Albany. 4 p. 8vo. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 342. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Parma, [Mich.,] Mar 30, 1850, to James J. Strang at Buffalo. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 343. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Parma, [Mich.,] Jul 20, 1850, to James J. Strang at Beaver Island. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 344. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Chicago, Oct. 28, [1850], to James J. Strang at Beaver Island. 3 p. foolscap. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 345. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Parma, [Mich.,] Jul 14, 1851, to James J. Strang. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 346. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Parma, [Mich.,] Jul 8, 1851, to James J. Strang at Detroit. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 347. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Parma, [Mich.,] Jul 10, 1851, to James J. Strang. 4 p. 8vo. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 348. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Parma, [Mich.,] Jul 27, 1851, to James J. Strang at Beaver Island. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 349. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Parma, [Mich.,] Jul 30, 1851, to Miss Elizabeth McNutt [later Strang's second plural wife]. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 350. SAMUEL GRAHAM. ALS, dated Parma, [Mich.,] Aug 24, 1851, to James J. Strang at Mackinac. 4 p. 8vo. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 351. CHARLES GREENWOOD. ALS, dated Boston, Jul 1, 1849, to James J. Strang at Voree. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 352. JAMES M. GREIG. ALS, dated New Brighton, [Pa.], Dec 29, 186, to James J. Strang at Voree. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 353. JAMES M. GREIG. ALS, dated New Brighton, [Pa.,] Mar 29, 1849, to James J. Strang at Burlington. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 354. JAMES M. GREIG. ALS, dated Troy, [Beaver Island], Nov 16, 1849, to James J. Strang at New York. 5 p. 8vo; 3 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 355. JAMES M. GREIG. ALS, dated Troy, Beaver Island, Feb 28, 1850, to James J. Strang at Washington, D. C. 2 p. foolscap [slightly damaged]. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 356. JAMES M. GREIG. ALS, dated Beaver Island, Aug 26, [1850?], to James J. Strang, Beaver Island. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 357. JOHN W. GRIERSON. ALS, dated Akron, Ohio, Apr 30, 1851, to James J. Strang. 4 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 358. STEPHEN GRIFFITH. ALS, dated Maumee City, Ohio, Nov 11, 1849, to the Church of Latter Day Saints at Beaver Island. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 359. ALDEN HALE. ALS, dated [n.p.] May 13, 1848, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 360. ALDEN HALE. ALS, dated Lowell, [Mass.,] Dec 2, 1848, to James J. Strang. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 361. ALDEN HALE. ALS, dated [Lowell, Mass., Jan 1, 1849], to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 362. ALDEN HALE. ALS, dated North Bay, Oneida Co., N.Y. Apr 13, 1849, to James J. Strang. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 363. ALDEN HALE. ALS, dated [n.p.] Apr 16, 1849, to James J. Strang at Voree. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 364. ALDEN HALE. ALS, dated Alexander, N.Y., Apr 19, 1849, to James J. Strang, with postscript by Reuben T. Nichols. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 365. ALDEN HALE. ALS, dated [Burlington, Wis.] Mar 7, 1850, to William Skimmins at Boston. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 366. J. C. HALL. ALS, dated Buffalo, Sep 23, 1850, to James J. Strang at Beaver Island. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 367. O. H. HARVEY. ALS, dated Hampton, Ill., Apr 28, 1846, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 368. RICHARD and ELIZABETH HAZELETH [?] ALS, dated [n.p.] Sep 22, 1850, to James J. Strang at Voree. 2 p. 8vo. [damaged] (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 369. DAVID HEATH. ALS, dated Cleveland, Ohio, Jul 22, 1851, to James J. Strang at Beaver Island. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 370. HENRY P. HERRON. ALS, dated Kirtland, Ohio, May 31, 1846, to John E. Page or Jehiel Savage at Voree, 1 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 371. PETER HESS. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Aug 13, 1849, to James J. Strang at Beaver Island. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 372. PETER HESS. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Oct 23, 1849, to James J. Strang at New York City. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 373. PETER HESS. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Dec 4, 1849, to James J. Strang. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 374. PETER HESS. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Dec 12, 1849, to James J. Strang. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 375. PETER HESS. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Oct 24, 1849, to James J. Strang at New York City. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 376. PETER HESS. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Dec 25, 1849, to James J. Strang, with additions signed by Amos Lowen. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 377. PETER HESS. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Jan 2, 1850, to James J. Strang. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 378. PETER HESS. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Jan 8, 1850, to James J. Strang. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 379. PETER HESS. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Jan 19, 1850, to James J. Strang. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 380. PETER HESS. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Jan 17, 1850, to Bro. ---- Hosmer. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 381. PETER HESS. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Feb 13, 1850, to James J. Strang. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 382. PETER HESS. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Apr 3, 1850, to James J. Strang at Buffalo. 1 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 383. LORENZO DOW HICKEY. ALS, dated Armada, Mich., Sep 26 and Oct 11, 1846, to James J. Strang at Voree. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 384. L. D. HICKEY. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Dec 6, 1849, to James J. Strang. [In same letter:] ANDREW G. JACKSON. ALS, dated Dec 6, 1849, to James J. Strang. 4 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 385. L. D. HICKEY. ALS, dated Philadelphia, [Dec] 12, 1849, to James J. Strang at Baltimore. 3 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 386. L. D. HICKEY. ALS, dated [Philadelphia, ca. Dec 24, 1849], to James J. Strang at Baltimore. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 387. L. D. HICKEY. ALS, dated Lapeer, [Mich.,] Apr 13, 1850. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 388. L. D. HICKEY. ALS, dated Lapeer, [Mich.,] Aug 14, 1850, to James J. Strang at Beaver Island. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 389. THOMAS R. HICKS. ALS, dated New Britain, [ ], Jan 16, 1847, to James J. Strang at Voree. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 390. ABIGAIL D. HOLMES. ALS, dated Georgetown, Mass., Oct 6, 1850, to James J. Strang at Beaver Island. 4 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 391. I. A. HOPKINS. Letter dated Milwaukie, Wis., Nov 28, 1846, to James J. Strang at Voree. l p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 392. I. A. HOPKINS. Letter dated Milwaukee, Dec 28, 1846, to James J. Strang at Burlington. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 393. I. A. HOPKINS. Letter dated Milwaukee, Jul 26, 1849, to James J. Strang. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 394. LYDIA HUBBARD. ALS, dated Chenango, [N.Y.], Aug 14, 1850, to James J. Strang. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 395. LEN HUBBELL. ALS, dated Milwaukee, Wis., Jul 12, 1849, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 396. WILLIAM L. HUGHEY. ALS, dated Galena, [Ill.,] Jun 28, 1846, to John E. Page at Voree. 1 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 397. ANDREW G. JACKSON. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Nov 22, 1849, to James J. Strang. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 398. ANDREW G. JACKSON. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Nov 26, 1849, to James J. Strang. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 399. ANDREW G. JACKSON. ALS, dated Pottsville, Pa., Jan 3, 1850, to Thomas Braidwood at Philadelphia. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 400. ANDREW G. JACKSON. ALS, dated Pottsville, [Pa.,] Dec 31, 1849, to Peter Hess. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 401. ANDREW G. JACKSON. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Jan 24, 1850, to James J. Strang at Baltimore. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 402. ANDREW G. JACKSON. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Mar 15, 1850, to James J. Strang at New York City. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 403. J. W. JENKS. ALS, dated Ossining, N.Y., Apr 16, 1846, to James J. Strang at Burlington, Wis. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 404. J. W. JENKS. ALS, dated New York, Oct 24, 1846, to James J. Strang at Voree. 3 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 405. JOHN JORDAN. ALS, dated St. Charles, [Ill.], Nov 30, 1846 to James J. Strang at Voree. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 406. ANDREW KETCHUM. ALS, dated Perry, Ind., Aug 18, 1850, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 407. JOSEPH R. KETCHAM. ALS, dated Oswego, [N.Y.,] Nov 9, 1846, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 408. ABSALOM KUYKENDALL. ALS, dated Crescent City, Iowa, Feb 5, 1860 to E. & E. Strang. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 409. ANSEL LAKE. ALS, dated Milo [ ], May 28, 1850, to "Brother Chidester." 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 410. ANSEL LAKE. ALS, dated Compton, Ill., Jun 11, 1851, to James J. Strang at Lansing, Mich. 1 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 411. MARY LEATHERBURY. ALS, dated [Allensville, La.(?)], Apr 13, 1849, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 412. EDWARD LEARNED. ALS, dated "Troy Road," Apr 1, 1850, to James J. Strang at Albany. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 413. M. LINDLEY. ALS, dated Baltimore, Nov 15, 1849, to George J. Adams at Baltimore. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - [See: MS draft of reply by Strang himself, Nov 19, 1849.] (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 414. M. L. LOCKWOOD. ALS, dated Vienna, [Mich.] Jun 15, 1851, James J. Strang at Detroit. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 415. AMOS LOWEN. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Oct 22, 1849, to James J. Strang at New York City. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 416. AMOS LOWEN. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Jan 1, 1850, to James J. Strang at Baltimore. 3 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 417. AMOS LOWEN. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Jan 10, 1850, to James J. Strang. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 418. AMOS LOWEN. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Jun 22, 1850, to James J. Strang at Beaver Island. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 419. AMOS LOWEN. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Oct 5, 1850, to James J. Strang. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 420. AMOS LOWEN. ALS, dated Philadelphia, [Dec] 7, 1850, to James J. Strang at Beaver Island. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 421. AMOS LOWEN. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Jun 15, 1851, to James J. Strang at Beaver Island. 3 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 422. JOHN MACAULEY. ALS, dated Galena, Ill., Jun 24, 1849, to James J. Strang at Voree. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 423. JOHN MACAULEY. ALS, dated Galena, Ill., Jul 15, 1849, to James J. Strang at Voree. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 424. JOHN MACAULEY. ALS, dated Galena, Ill., Jun 21, 1850, to Francis Cooper at Voree. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 425. R. W. McCLELLAND. LS, dated Washington, D. C., Jun 29, 1855, to James J. Strang at Beaver Island. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 426. H. D. McCULLOCH. ALS, dated St. James, [Mich.,] to James J. Strang, Nov 13, 1855. 1 p. 8vo. in pencil. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 427. WILLIAM MARKS. ALS, dated Shabbonas Grove, [Ill.,] May 23, 1847 to James J. Strang at Burlington. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 428. F. MERRYWEATHER. ALS, dated Springfield, Ky., Oct 11, 1846, to James J. Strang at Voree. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 429. F. MERRYWEATHER. ALS, dated Nashville, [Tenn.,] Oct 25, 1846, to James J. Strang at Voree. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 430. ISAAC B. MEYERS. ALS, dated Euphemia, [Ohio], Dec 23, 1849, to James J. Strang at Washington. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 431. MARK MILLER. ALS, dated Racine, [Wis.,] Sep 2, 1850, to James J. Strang. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 432. MARK MILLER. ALS, dated Racine [Wis.], Oct 1, 1850, to James J. Strang. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 433. MARK MILLER. ALS, dated Racine, [Wis.,] Dec 23, 1850, to James J. Strang at Beaver Island. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 434. E. J. MOORE. ALS, dated City of James, [Beaver Island, Mich.,] Oct 6, 1849, to Samuel Graham at New York City. 4 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 435. E. J. MOORE. ALS, dated Beaver Island, Jun 20, 1850, to A. Wadsworth, Grand Travers, Mich., per James J. Strang. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 436. JOEL [?] MURRAY. ALS, dated Turtle, [ ], Jul 22, 1849, to James J. Strang. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 437. EBEN NASH. ALS, dated Chicago, Sep 23, 1850, to James J. Strang at Beaver Island. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 438. URIAH C. H. NICKERSON. ALS, dated [n.p.] Mar 27, 1846, to Reuben Miller at Voree. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 439. JESSE W. NICHOLS. ALS, dated New Bedford, Mass., Mar 4, 1847, to James J. Strang at Voree. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 440. JESSE W. NICHOLS. ALS, dated North Dartmouth, [Mass.,] Nov 10, 1849, to James J. Strang at New York City. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 441. JESSE W. NICHOLS. ALS, dated North Dartmouth, Mass., Dec 28, 1849, to James J. Strang at Baltimore. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 442. JESSE W. NICHOLS. ALS, dated North Dartmouth, Mass., Jan 3, 1850, to James J. Strang at Baltimore. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 443. R. T. NICHOLS. ALS, dated Chicago, Jul 22, 1846, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 444. R. T. NICHOLS. ALS, dated Clayton, [N.Y.,] Dec 15, 1846, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 445. JAMES D. NIXON. ALS, dated Potosi, Wis., Jan 9, 1850, to C. J. Douglass [Elvira Field] at Baltimore. 4 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 446. T. NIXON. ALS, dated Chicago, May 1, 1846, to James J. Strang at Voree. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 447. SAMUEL NORTHUP. ALS, dated Alexandria, [N.Y.,] Mar 9, 1846, to James J. Strang at Burlington, Wis. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 448. CHARLES O'MALLEY. ALS, dated Mackinac, [Mich.,] Apr 25, 1850, to James J. Strang at Beaver Island. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 449. CHARLES O'MALLEY. ALS, dated Mackinac, [Mich.,] Apr 25, 1850, to James J. Strang. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 450. TULLY O'MALLEY. ALS, dated Mackinac, [Mich.,] May 2, 1850, to James J. Strang at Beaver Island. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 451. ISAAC PADEN. ALS, dated [Knoxville, Ill.,] Apr 4 [1], 1846, to James M. Adams at Burlington, Wis. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 452. ISAAC PADEN. ALS, dated Knoxville, Ill., Feb 19, 1847, to James J. Strang at Voree. 4 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 453. ANGELINE PAGE. MS communication dated Jun 6, 1856, to unnamed correspondent. 3 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 454. EBENEZER PAGE. ALS, dated Black River, Jefferson Co., N.Y., Oct 17, 1846, to James J. Strang at Voree. 3 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 455. EBENEZER PAGE. ALS, dated [Canton? N.Y.] Nov 28, 1846, to James J. Strang at Voree, with a postscript by Milo Weston. 3 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 456. EBENEZER PAGE. ALS, dated Lockport, [N.Y.,] Jan 19, 1847, to James J. Strang at Voree. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 457. EBENEZER PAGE. ALS, dated Attica, N.Y., Mar 7, 1850, to James J. Strang, at Washington. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 458. I. J. [?] PATTEN. ALS, dated Voree, [Wis.] Dec 3, 1849 to James J. Strang at Washington. 1 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 459. JOHN C. PEIRCE. ALS, dated Boston, Nov 7, 1850, to James J. Strang at Beaver Island. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 460. JOHN C. PEIRCE. ALS, dated Boston, May 10, 1851, to James J. Strang at Beaver Island. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 461. ELISHA PERSONS. ALS, dated Brownshelm, O., Apr 18, 1849, to James J. Strang at Voree. 3 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 462. B. [?] PIERCE. ALS, dated [n.p.] Aug 9, 1861, to L. D. Hickey. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 463. ISAAC PIERCE. ALS, City of James Beaver Nov 6, 1849, to James J. Strang at New York City. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 464. ANDREW J. PORTER and A. W. PRINDLE. ALS, dated Voree, Dec 26, 1849, to James J. Strang at Washington. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 465. STEPHEN POST. ALS, dated Centreville, Pa., Apr 20, 1849, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 466. STEPHEN POST. ALS, dated Centreville, Pa., Aug 23, 1849, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 467. STEPHEN POST. ALS, dated Centreville, Pa., Jan 27, 1850. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 468. STEPHEN POST. ALS, dated Centreville, Pa., Mar 3, 1850, to James J. Strang at New York City. 1 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 469. STEPHEN POST. ALS, dated Centreville, Pa., Jun 7, 1850, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 470. EDWARD PRESTON. ALS, dated [Rivestown?] Md., Nov 19, 1849, to James J. Strang at Baltimore. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 471. EDWARD PRESTON. ALS, dated Westminster, Md., Dec 5, 1849, to James J. Strang at Baltimore. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 472. EDWARD PRESTON. ALS, dated Springport, [Mich.,] Nov 12, 1850, to James J. Strang at Beaver Island. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 473. E. D. RANSOM. ALS, dated Belvidere, Ill., Jun 30, 1849, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 474. WILLIAM RAUNSELER [?] ALS, dated Chicago, Jan 4, 1847, to James J. Strang at Burlington, Wis. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 475. CHARLES RIDLOW. ALS, dated Beloit, Wis., Oct 21, 1850, to James J. Strang. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 476. D. ROUTZEN. ALS, dated Finley, Ohio, Mar 13, 1847, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 477. CHARLES A. ROGERS. ALS, dated New Bedford, Mass., Mar 27, 1850, to James J. Strang. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 478. STRATTEN ROGERS. ALS, dated [Beaver Island?], Apr 3, 1851, to James J. Strang. 1 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 479. WILLIAM ROSE. ALS, dated Binghamton, N.Y., Oct 5, 1846, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 480. CATHERINE SAVAGE. ALS, dated Bigelow's Mills, Ia., Jan. 8 1849, to James J. Strang, Burlington, Wis. 1 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 481. MURRY SEAMAN. ALS, dated Mackinac, [Mich.] Jul 20, 1851, to James J. Strang at Beaver Island. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 482. MURRY SEAMAN. ALS, dated Drummond, [Mich.?] Nov 11, 1859, to J. M. Wait and H. G. Hall. 4 p. 8vo. in pencil. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 483. JESSE SEELYE. ALS, dated Savannah, N.Y., Dec 6, 1846, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 484. WILLIAM S. SEGAR. ALS, dated Utica, N.Y., Dec 30, 1846, to James J. Strang, at Voree. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 485. SAMUEL SHAW. ALS, dated Elgin, Ill., Jun 1, 1846, to James J. Strang at Voree. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 486. GEORGE M. SHIPPEN. ALS, dated Milwaukee, Mar 31, 1846, to James J. Strang at Burlington, Wis. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 487. DAVID SHOOK. ALS, dated Mount Clemens. [ ], May 26, 1856, to James J. Strang. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 488. A. SIAS [?], JR. ALS, dated McHenry, Ill., Feb 23, 1849, [to James J. Strang?] 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 489. JOHN SMALL. ALS, dated Aldon, Wis., Apr 8, 1847, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 490. WEALTHY SMITH. ALS, dated Hanover, [N.Y.,] Nov 1, 1846, James J. Strang at Burlington. 3 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 491. WILLIAM SMITH. ALS, dated Kirtland, O., Aug 20, 1846, to James J. Strang at Philadelphia. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 492. WILLIAM SMITH. ALS, dated Knoxville, Ill., Dec 2, 1846, to James J. Strang at Burlington, Wis. 4 p. foolscap; 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 493. FREDERIC SQUIRE. ALS, dated French Creek [N.Y.,] Apr 3, 1850, to James J. Strang at Voree. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 494. RICHARD STEPHENS. ALS, dated Louisville, Ill., Mar 8, [1846], to James J. Strang at Burlington. 1 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 495. RICHARD STEPHENS. ALS, dated Louisville, Ill., Mar 16, 1847, to M. L. Perce at Burlington, Wis. 1 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 496. ROYAL STONE. ALS, dated Vienna [N.Y.?], Aug 19, 1849, to James J. Strang at Voree. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 497. ABIJAH R. TEWKSBURY. ALS, dated Boston, Apr 3, 1847, to James J. Strang at Voree. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 498. SAUL E. THOMPSON. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Sep 23, 1846, to James J. Strang at New York City. 3 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 499. LORENZO TUBBS. ALS, dated Hodi [?Shade?], O., May 3, 1849, to James J. Strang at Burlington, Wis. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 500. HIRAM TUCKER. ALS, dated Antwerp, [N.Y.,] May 15, 1846, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 501. JOHN URSBRUCK. ALS, dated Philadelphia, Aug 13, 1849, to James J. Strang at Beaver Island. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 502. F. A. UTTER. ALS, dated Elkhorn, [Wis.,] May 16, 1846, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 503. LEWIS VAN BUREN. ALS, dated Madison, Ia. Mar 14, 1846, to James J. Strang at Burlington. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 504. LEWIS VAN BUREN. ALS, dated Madison, [Ia.], May 6, 1846, to James J. Strang at Burlington. 3 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 505. J. M. WAIT. ALS, dated St. James, Beaver Island, [Mich.,] Dec 1, 1855, to James J. Strang. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 506. MOORE WALKER. ALS, dated New York, Feb 2, 1850 to James J. Strang at Washington. 2 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 507. GEORGE WALTER. ALS, dated Kingston, Mo., Jul 11, 1847, to James J. Strang at Voree. 1 p. 8vo. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 508. GILBERT WATSON. ALS, dated Voree, Sep 19, 1849, to James J. Strang at Buffalo. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 510. GILBERT WATSON. ALS, dated Little Woods, Kane Co., Ill. Nov 3, [1849], to James J. Strang at Baltimore. 2 p. foolscap. (Box 2, Folder 46)